const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What does SQL stand for?",
        choices : [
            "Strong Question Language",
            "Structured Query Language",
            "Structured Question Language"
        ],
        answer: "Structured Query Language"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which SQL statement is used to extract data from a database?",
        choices : [
            "EXTRACT",
            "SELECT",
            "GET",
            "OPEN"
        ],
        answer: "SELECT"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which SQL statement is used to update data in a database?",
        choices : [
            "MODIDY",
            "UPDATE",
            "SAVE",
            "SAVE AS"
        ],
        answer: "UPDATE"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which SQL statement is used to delete data from a database?",
        choices : [
            "REMOVE",
            "DELETE",
            "COLLAPSE"
        ],
        answer: "DELETE"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which SQL statement is used to insert new data in a database?",
        choices : [
            "INSERT INTO",
            "ADD RECORD",
            "INSERT NEW",
            "ADD NEW"
        ],
        answer: "INSERT INTO"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "With SQL, how do you select a column named 'FirstName' from a table named 'Persons'?",
        choices : [
            "SELECT FirstName FROM Persons",
            "EXTRACT FirstName FROM Persons",
            "SELECT Persons.FirstName"
        ],
        answer: "SELECT FirstName FROM Persons"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "With SQL, how do you select all the columns from a table named 'Persons'?",
        choices : [
            "SELECT * FROM Persons",
            "SELECT [all] FROM Persons",
            "SELECT *.Persons",
            "SELECT Persons"
        ],
        answer: "SELECT * FROM Persons"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "With SQL, how do you select all the records from a table named 'Persons' where the value of the column 'FirstName' is 'Peter'?",
        choices : [
            "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName<>'Peter'",
            "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName='Peter'",
            "SELECT [all] FROM Persons WHERE FirstName='Peter'",
            "SELECT [all] FROM Persons WHERE FirstName LIKE 'Peter'"
        ],
        answer: "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName='Peter'"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "With SQL, how do you select all the records from a table named 'Persons' where the value of the column 'FirstName' starts with an 'a'?",
        choices : [
            "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName LIKE '%a'",
            "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName LIKE 'a%'",
            "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName='a'",
            "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName='%a%'"
        ],
        answer: "SELECT * FROM Persons WHERE FirstName LIKE 'a%'"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "The OR operator displays a record if ANY conditions listed are true. The AND operator displays a record if ALL of the conditions listed are true",
        choices : [
            true, 
            false
        ],
        answer: true
    }
]

export default questions
